This Golda Briones,
how sure are you that she's not
an asset for the enemy?
15 million pesos in one year.
His rank is Major.
Even a full colonel won't make
that money in ten years.
If I get suspended,
I can accept it.
I don't care what they say.
But if my own family
abandons me...
There's a CCTV that doesn't
belong to the village.
They didn't clean it up.
So it's a she.
We're looking for a woman.
That's what suits you
with all your slandering
of Major Delgado!
Dizon's exposé didn't help.
You are placed under preventive
suspension.
Pending full investigation.
It's easy for you to say
that my father is a bad person.
You don't care about the lives
of the people you're slandering!
You only think about yourself!
You're so mean, Joey!
Why did you do that?
You're so brave!
I'm not afraid of him.
Even if he sues you?
Yes.
I won't back down from him.
Okay...
Uncle.
Peter.
It's good that you're here.
There's a new delivery of wires.
Make an inventory
in the stockroom.
Okay, Uncle.
You know, if that Andrew
sues you,
Aunt Clarissa will have even
more problems.
I was just defending my father.
He doesn't deserve
to be bashed online.
Good morning.
Are you the owner here?
Yes, it's me.
What can I do for you?
Are you the ones who installed
the CCTV in District One?
Yes, it's us. Why?
We need to recover some
recorded video.
But someone said one of your
employee already went
to update it, so it was deleted.
Who is that?
Is there someone there?
What are you doing there?
Peter, one of the guys outside,
is among those who I took
the video of in the alley.
Peter, come here first.
Just stay here.
Yes?
Uncle?
Who updated the system
in District One?
Is it scheduled?
What? Do you know anything
about the system update
they're talking about?
No, I don't know.
I'm sure it wasn't me,
so I don't know.
Sir, I'll check with my other
staff first, okay?
Maybe they updated it.
But in the logbook,
it's not yet scheduled.
Do you have a female staff
member here?
We're looking for someone.
A woman? Yes, there is.
That's Precious, my secretary.
Is it her that
you're looking for?
No.
Gentlemen, do you need
anything else?
We're a bit busy.
- Nothing more. Thank you.
- Thank you. Okay.
That girl is driving me crazy.
What? Do you want to sue her
for trespassing?
Assault?
We have footage here.
We have a recording
of what she did.
No, no need. Let's not make
a big deal out of it.
It's easy for you to say
that my father is a bad person!
Because you hate the police!
You're the one who's biased!
You don't care about the lives
of the people you're ruining.
You're smart.
But that's all you have.
Brains but no heart!
Wait, where are you going?
Aren't we going to finish
the recording?
Well, we're almost done
cleaning up here.
Let's call it a day.
Peter.
Are you sure the footage
where I was captured
is no longer in the system?
Yes.
I deleted it all.
On the main drive, in the bin,
in the recycle bin. Everything!
Even an IT expert can't find
anything there.
So I don't have to worry.
But why did they ask your uncle
if he had a female employee?
That means they knew they
had to find a female.
It seems that way.
But how?
You didn't tell anyone else,
did you?
Of course not.
And you?
Of course not either.
Why did you delete it?
This only brings a problem.
There's already a lot going on
in my life, in my family,
this also adds to it.
All the cargo units,
sealed and tagged, Boss.
The ETA is less than 48 hours.
All the plate numbers are fake.
And all the escorts
are paid for too.
That's a whopping 500 million
dollar drug shipment.
We can't afford another fiasco.
We lost too much already.
Exactly.
That's what I told Matias.
No checkpoints.
No leaks.
I've also changed the routes
of our supply chain.
That easy?
Customs and coast guards
have tightened up
after our shipment was busted.
How'd you do it?
Okay.
I get it.
You have networks.
That's why I partnered with you.
But what if there's
a smart-aleck again?
What's that name?
Officer Miguel Delgado?
He's not our problem anymore.
He's in stitches
over Ramon's death.
I'm sure he's already been
implicated in the investigation.
Parak is focused on him.
Joey, who are you looking
at there?
Are you waiting for someone?
Nothing, Mother.
Are you thinking if your father
will visit us?
Sorry, Joey.
I can't really forgive him yet.
I can't face him yet.
But that doesn't mean you have
to feel the same way.
Whatever your father's
shortcomings and sins...
that's only on me.
You don't have to carry that.
I also know that you miss
your father so much.
So if you want to check
on him...
meet and talk to him...
I won't stop you.
But please, Joey...
don't force me to make peace
with him either.
I can't do it yet.
Yes, Mother.
- Give me!
- It's not possible, Ma'am.
Give me the medicine.
Ma'am...
Give me that!
Get out of here!
Give me my medicine!
I'm in pain!
- Mom! Mom!
- Andrew, Andrew, please.
Please, Andrew.
Give me, give me.
She doesn't want to give me
my medicine.
She doesn't want to give it.
She's being greedy.
Give me.
Maybe we can increase
my mom's dosage
because she's already
in so much pain. You see.
Andrew, no!
If we give her more,
she'll overdose.
So be it!
I'd rather die to end
this suffering!
Get out of this room
if you don't want to give me
my medicine.
Get out!
Get out! You, especially you!
Get out of here!
Get out! Get out...
Andrew, make her leave.
Get her out of here!
Andrew...
There are days she's
just like that.
Needing more meds.
Maybe we can talk to the doctor
to increase mom's dosage?
Andrew, mom's dosage
is already high.
But she's still in pain.
She's always in pain.
Remember what the doctor said?
That's why we're managing
her meds as best we can.
But her painkillers
are wearing off quickly.
Anyway, have you eaten yet?
I'll ask our nanny to prepare
something for you, okay?
Wait here.
Yes, we received the payment.
Thank you again.
It's really nice doing business
with you.
Until next time.
Is that Mr. Lee?
Yes.
The shipment landed,
and he's thrilled.
He also said that our items
are top-tier quality.
And guess what?
He wants exclusivity.
Great.
So that means the next price
will be higher.
We have another piece
of good news.
We didn't just silenced Delgado.
He's still the number one
suspect in Ramon's death.
Poor Delgado.
A fall guy and a scapegoat.
The stars are finally aligning
in favor of us again.
Speaking of Ramon,
does Loloy have an update
on what I'm looking for?
Vote straight, Kalasag Party!
Zoom in. Close up, that's all.
It's so boring.
What's with you?
Didn't you agree to be
my assistant
so you could make money?
You know, Andrew, instead
of complaining all the time,
just watch what I do
so you can learn something.
Where are you going?
I'll just go to the CR.
Go, go, go, go.
Mom! Mom...
Andrew!
Mom!
Mom.
- Son.
- Mom.
Help!
Mr. Dizon,
Ma'am, good morning.
The Special Investigations
Unit's initial report
is complete.
And based on the available
forensic and ballistic analysis,
your mother was not the primary
target.
She was one of the several
casualties during the crossfire.
Don't tell me it was a crossfire
because there was no shooting
around her.
That was not a stray bullet.
The intention was to shoot
my mom.
We reviewed the CCTV
and crowd footage.
We did not see a clear angle
of the shooter.
The slug that was recovered
did not match the gun we found
at the site.
And there is also no witness who
can corroborate your statement
that your mother was
specifically targeted.
You're closing a case
based on lack of evidence
while my mom is in the hospital,
dying right now.
I understand your frustrations,
Mr. Dizon.
But unless we get a new evidence
or a witness
who can testify
to your statement,
the case will remain closed.
The official ruling
is collateral fatality.
Useless police officers!
Just say that you're covering up
for someone.
This is a cover-up.
It's easy for you to say
that my father is a bad person!
Because you're mad
at the police!
You're the one who's biased!
They've traced the CCTV
in the office.
Just a little patience,
we'll track down that woman too.
Very good.
I can't wait to meet her
face-to-face...
so that I'll be the one
filming her
while she's crying,
scared, and begging.
Because she made a mistake
with whom she messed up with.
Relax, Joey.
You're getting paranoid.
Joey Delgado, Ma'am?
Yes.
Let's go.
Well, there's another scenario.
We were all stuck in the mud,
then, after our training,
we took a shower together.
Then, there was someone else
with us.
Do you remember Herera?
- Herera, yes.
- I remember him.
What was he wearing?
Not a brief.
Panty!
The life of a suspended officer
is pretty good, isn't it?
Just laughing and drinking.
Instead of fixing the problem,
he's getting wasted!
Maybe what they're accusing him
of is true.
Who do you think he is, a saint?
When he is hiding so many sins.
Buddy...
He wants to fight.
Look, he stood up.
Don't.
Don't pay attention.
Ignore them, Bro.
Let's just continue chatting.
Let's go!
Waiter!
Who's that?
Isn't that Boss Idol?
The one in Ka-Tirada.
- Yes, that's him.
- Isn't that him?
That's him.
That's him, isn't it?
Boss Idol.
Yes.
My condolences.
Thank you.
How did you meet my husband?
We don't know each
other personally.
Actually, I'm here for you.
Okay, Mother,
I'm on my way home.
Take care. I love you!
Sir, can you hurry up, please?
Why?
Just hurry up, Sir.
My mother needs me.
Okay.
My husband is kind.
But we have four children.
Life is very hard.
His meager salary can no
longer support our family.
But sometimes, I was surprised.
He had a lot of money
and I made him confess.
He also couldn't hide it.
He admitted that he was
doing some illegal things.
Sir, at the next corner,
turn right.
Ma'am, that will
be a longer route.
It's okay.
I need to buy medicine
for my mother.
I'll just add a tip for you.
Okay, it's up to you.
Just hurry up, please, Sir.
I stopped him several times,
but he said it was safe.
Until one day, he looked
so scared when he got home.
He said he had to hide.
I said, let's go get help.
Well, if he had just told
the truth but he said he can't
because Parak would kill him.
Parak?
Is Miguel Delgado the
one he was referring to?
I'm not sure who he was
referring to,
but I'm sure
it wasn't Major Delgado.
Because the day Ramon
disappeared,
he left something with me.
He said, if anything bad
happens to him,
I'll give it to Miguel Delgado.
We've got a lot of people
with us.
What a poor guy!
He's sulking!
That's because his family
left him!
Because what he did
was shameful!
He deserves that!
What did you say?
Bro, ignore them.
It's true!
Didn't your wife and daughter
leave you?
You don't have a career anymore!
You don't have a family anymore!
Do you know what you're called?
Loser!
Enough, Bro! Enough!
Dude, enough! Enough!
Dude, enough!
Enough!
That's enough!
Enough, Bro!
Who's the loser now?
Thank you.
Mother.
Joey, why are you home late?
I just passed by somewhere.
I'm sure you're hungry.
- Right?
- Yes.
Come on, come on.
Perfect timing,
I'm done cooking.
Metropolitan State University.
That's the video you took.
It's wrong to delete that video.
I'll take care of this.
Why do you need to install CCTV?
We need to make sure Joey
doesn't have a stalker.
What if someone gets
into this house?
What if someone tries
to kill me again, Andrew?
Do you know my daughter,
Joey Delgado?
She went to the market.
Who are you?
Jay's Pro Gym. JPG?
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Did you see a woman
in a red jacket?
My sister ran away from me.
Boss, he's here.
Good job, Parak.
What do you need from
the woman you're after?
Hey! Get in the car!
Your husband is a suspect
in the death
of Staff Sergeant Ramon Orbos.
I have evidence!
You can't take my father.
It's time to meet that freaking
girl and get that video.